Title: Asaf Avidan - One day / Reckoning Song (Wankelmut Remix)
Cej I  

Dm F  C  Bb ...

One day baby, we'll be old
Oh baby, we'll be old
And think of all the stories that we could have told

No more tears, my heart is dry
I don't laugh and I don't cry
I don't think about you all the time
But when I do I wonder why

You have to go out of my door
And leave just like you did before
I know I said that I was sure
But rich men can't imagine poor.

One day baby, we'll be old
Oh baby, we'll be old
And think of all the stories that we could have told

Little me and little you
Kept doing all the things they do
They never really think it through
Like I can never think you're true

Here I go again  the blame
The guilt, the pain, the hurt, the shame
The founding fathers of our plane
That's stuck in heavy clouds of rain.

One day baby, we'll be old
Oh baby, we'll be old
And think of all the stories that we could have told. 
Length: 03:31